(Sheldon:)...to verify the identity
of one's coconspirators.
PENNY: Is that Raj and Howard?
- Possibly, but unverified.
Would you just let us in?
(Sheldon:)Luckily for you,
this is not a nuclear reactor.
So, what'd you get the birthday boy?
(Howard:)Raj got him an awesome
limited-edition Dark Knight sculpture...
(Howard:)...based on Alex Ross'
definitive Batman.
(Howard:)And I got him this amazing autographed
copy of The Feynman Lectures on Physics.
(Penny:)Nice. I got him a sweater.
(Howard:)Okay, well, he might like that.
I've seen him get chilly.
(Penny:)- Sheldon, I didn't see your present.
- That's because I didn't bring one.
(Penny:)- Why not?
- Don't ask.
The entire institution of gift-giving
makes no sense.
- Too late.
- Let's say I go out and I spend $50 on you.
(Sheldon:)It's a laborious activity
because I have to imagine what you need...
...where you know what you need.
I could simplify things,
just give you the $50 directly...
...and then you could give me $50
on my birthday and so on...
(Sheldon:)...until one of us dies,
leaving the other one old and $50 richer.